<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TechTrends</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">I agree to these <b>terms</b> &amp; <b> conditions</b> </string>
    <string name="tos_content">
        &lt;h5&gt;

        Privacy Policy

        &lt;/h5&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        I take your privacy very seriously.

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends&lt;/b&gt;

        does not collect any user data, and all sensitive information (passwords and other account information) is
        stored securely in the local application database on your device.

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends&lt;/b&gt;

        will use the following permissions to provide you with the service.

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        - Access Network permission (to access online content as you specify)

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        - Get network status permission (to determine if the device currently has available network conditions)

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        - Background service permission (to automatically sync your favorites for you on a regular
        basis)

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;

        Third Party Services

        &lt;/h5&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        This policy does not apply to third-party services that you use with &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends &lt;/b&gt;. You can review
        the privacy policies of the third-party services you use on their websites

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;

        Disclaimers

        &lt;/h5&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends&lt;/b&gt;

        is a content collection tool only. Your use of &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends&lt;/b&gt; is subject to the laws and
        regulations of your country and region, and any liability arising from your actions will be borne by you
        personally.

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;

        Open Source License

        &lt;/h5&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends&lt;/b&gt;

        is an open source project under the GNU GPL 3.0 Open Source License[1], which allows you to use, reference, and
        modify the source code of &lt;b&gt;Tech Trends&lt;/b&gt; free of charge, but does not allow the
        modified and derived code to be distributed and sold as closed-source commercial software. For details, please
        see the full GNU GPL 3.0 Open Source License[2].

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;

        Appendix

        &lt;/h5&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        - [1] https://github.com/Fa-d/TechTrends

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;

        - [2] https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html

        &lt;/p&gt;
    </string>
</resources>